Register to The Charles Ives Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series III; 13 boxes
  - Correspondence - General, III.A
    - Bellamann, Henry (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - John Kirkpatrick to above, 1957 Jan 14; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - John Kirkpatrick to Jones, Miriam, 1959 Apr 23; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - 1964 Sep 25, typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Mandel, Elsa to John Kirkpatrick, 1961 Aug 31; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Dolarhide, Louis, 1964 Oct 28; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - John Kirkpatrick to above, 1964 Oct 31; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Bendiner, Milton, 1941 Nov 27; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
      See also III.A/31/8/Rovinsky
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Bendiner, 1942 Jan 12; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Charles Ives to Bennett, R.R., no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
      See also III.B/35/1/NAACC
    - Berger, Arthur, 1932 May 11; typed letter (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Berman, Anne
    - Bernstein, Leonard
      See:
      III.A/28/7/Cowell 1951 Mar 11
    - Beyer, Johanna M. for Henry Cowell, 1940 May 24; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Biart, Victor to Edith Ives, 1939 Mar 24; *typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Biggs, E. Power, 1948 Apr 15; typed letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Biggs, 1948 May 7; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives, no date; 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Biggs, 1948 Jul 13, Aug 9, 1949 Oct 19; 4 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - 1951 Apr 30, (enc script) (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Blackwell, Carrie, 1949 Jul 6, ? Dec 30; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Bloesch, Richard, 1952 Mar 24; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Boatwright, Helen to Harmony Twichell Ives, 1956 Feb 3; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Charles Ives to Bodansky, Mrs.[?], no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Boelke, Walter
      III.B/34/5/Bomart
    - Bonner, Kenneth, no date; announcement and card
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 3 draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Charles Ives (typed) with note, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Boonin, Joseph M.
      See X.D/67/17/Library Correspondence and gifts after 1955
    - Bounds, Charles E., 1950 Jul 5; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Brandin, Walter, 1949 Oct 25; typed letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Brandin, 1949 Dec 22; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Brandt, Shirley, 1940 Jul 5; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
      See also III.B/34/2/American Music Center
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Braunstein, Wm.
      See III.A/28/8
    - Brintnall, Robert, 1953 Feb 16; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Broder, Nathan
      III.A/30/14/Kirkpatrick 1951 Jun 10
    - Bronte, Duca de, 1933 Jan 9; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck
      See III.B/34/6/Committee for 1,000
    - Charles Ives to Brown, Edward, 1937 [??]; 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Brown, Edward, 1939 Jul 29, Aug 14; 2 typed letters (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Paula Valles, 1952 Nov 20; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - no date, autograph card signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Bumpus, John, 1933 Jun 14; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Burk, John N.
      See III.B/34/5/BSO (Secretary, Boston Symphony)
    - Harmony Twichell Ives to Burnett, John, 1952; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 9)
      Dec 10
    - Burnham [?], no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Burton, Frank, 1951 Mar 6; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Byroade, George, 1922 Oct 4; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Cadman, Charles, 1921 Mar 9; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to Cadman, 1921 Apr 11; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Cadman, Charles, 1943 Jan 26; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Cage, John to Harmony Twichell Ives, to Charles Ives, no date, no date; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to above, 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 10)
        See also III.A/30/3/Harrison 1947 May 13 and following
    - Camp, John Spencer, 1920 [?] Mar 8; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Campbell, Tipton, 1921 Mar 18; autograph card signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Capleton, Arnold, 1921 Apr 18, 1921 Aug 15, 1923 Dec 10; 3 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to above, 1921 Jun 24; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Carabo, Madeleine, 1946; autograph letter signed
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Carabo, 1948; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Carl, William C., 1923 Jun 12; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Carson, Robert, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - 1947 May 6, typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Elliott (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives to Carter with note Charles Ives, [1926?]; typed letter (fragment: copy) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Carter, 1927 Feb 19, [1928 Jan]; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives toward, 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to Carter, 1944 Jun 12; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - transcription of above by John Kirkpatrick (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Carter for American Music Center - CI Society, 1944 Oct 20; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives for 20 Oct 1944, no date; 2 drafts (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to Carter transcribed by John Kirkpatrick, 1946 Mar 14, 16, 1946 Apr 9; 3 autograph letters signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Charles Ives postscript for 1946 Apr 9, draft (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1954 [?], Oct 9, 1954 Dec 14; 3 autograph letters signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, no date; Christmas card with note (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Carter, Franklin Jr., 1922 Nov 16; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Cary, C.P., no date; typed letter signed
      See Washington Life Insurance
    - Casella, Alfredo (State Symphony Orchestra of New York), 1925 Dec 30; typed letter signed with enc (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Charles Ives to Caturla, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chandler, Woods W., 1922 Oct 12; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chase, Gilbert (University of Oklahoma), 1955 Oct 2; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1947 Nov 23; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chase, Marian Tyler (Mrs. Stuart) 1952 Mar 21, 1952 Apr 4, 1952 Dec 15, 3 typed letters signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1952 Dec [?]; Christmas card
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to above, 1952 Mar 15; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to above, 1953 [?] Aug 28; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to above, 1954 Jun 23; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives to above, 1958 Apr 9; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chavanne [?], 1923 Jun 3; typed letter signed (in German) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Chavez, Carlos, 1936 Nov 12; typed letter (copy)
      with Charles Ives note
      - Chavez, 1936 Nov 12; typed letter signed (and copy) (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Clement, Henri Lloyd
      III.B/35/5/Native American Composers
      III.B/34/6/Co-ART Recording
    - Coe, Kenton, 1949 Oct 5; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Coerne, Louis A., 1921 Mar 5; typed letter signed and card (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Coffin, Mary and Caleb, no date; Christmas card (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Cohn, Arthur to Miss Stevenson (of Quality Photostat), 1935 Jul; 2 autograph letters signed
      - Cohn to Charles Ives, 1935 Jul 20 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to Arthur Cohn, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Cohn to Stevenson, 1935 Jul 27; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Cohn to Charles Ives, 1935 Jul 27 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to Guggenheim for Cohn, draft (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Coleman, John F., 1939 Jan 3, 11; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Collins, Anne
      See also X.D/67/17/Library Correspondence and gifts after 1955
      - Charles Ives to Collins, 1921 Aug 20; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Collins, Anne, envelope with note and address (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to Collins, 1921 Sep 17; autograph letter signed and envelope (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to Collins, 1928 [?] May 20; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Collins, 1942 May 19; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Collins, no date; Christmas card (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - New York Sun, 1921 Jul 7; clippings (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - "The Tender Gaoler", 1956 Jul 28; article (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Collins to Harmony Twichell Ives (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Comstock, Anne W., 1947 May 18; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Conley, Mrs. George (Kate), 1923 Mar 24; autograph letter signed
      - Conley, 1923 Apr 4; card (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to above, 1923 Mar 28; typed letter (copy) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Connelly, Norine B., 1950 Dec 8; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Conrad, Jean, 1952 May 20; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Conray, Florence and Tom, 1949 Dec 14; Christmas card (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Cook, Clement
      See X.D/66/8/Library Correspondence
    - Coolidge, Elizabeth S., 1921 Mar 15; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (not sent) (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Copland, Aaron (Box 27, Folder 13)
      III.B/34/2/American Music Center
      III.B/35/3/National Institute of Arts and Letters
      Photocopies of Charles Ives to Copland were given to V. Perlis by Copland in 1971
      - Copland, 1932 Apr 8; typed postcard with Charles Ives memo (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives to Copland, 1932 Jul 21; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Copland, 1933 Oct 7; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives for 1933 Oct 10, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives, 1933 Oct 10; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Charles Ives for 1934 May 24, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Copland, 1934 Jun 28; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Copland, 1943 Apr 22; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1946 Aug 18; autograph letter signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Copland to Perlis, 1970 Mar 5; typed letter signed (copy) (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Corelli, Keith to Putnam's, 1929 Jun 3; 2 typed letters signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - (Putnam's sent to Charles Ives), 1929 Jun 20 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Corelli, [?] May 8; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - no date, typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Corp, Paul, Helen, Charles, and Buddy, no date; Christmas card with note
      - Corp to Harmony Twichell Ives, no date; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - to Mrs. Pols re Corp, 1956 Aug 27; copy (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Cowell
      See Box 28
    - Crittenden, John C., 1951 Mar 4; postcard (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Crothers, Charles G., no date; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Cumpson, Harry, 1936 Apr 24; typed letter signed with enc
      - Cumpson, Harry, 1936 May 4; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - 1936 May 22, autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Charles Ives to above, no date; draft (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Cunningham, Loraine, 1945 May 8; typed letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Charles Ives to above, draft (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Cushman, Dora to Harmony Twichell Ives, 1909 Dec 22; autograph letter signed (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Cowell, Henry (Box 28, Folder 1)
      The originals of the Cowell correspondence were given to Sidney Cowell for the NYPL Cowell Collection by John Kirkpatrick. All below are photocopies unless indicated with the sign: **
      III.A/27/2/Babitz
      III.A/27/7/Bell 1939 Jan 19
      III.A/30/2/Harrison [1943 Jul ?]
      III.B/35/5,6,7,8/New Music
      III.B/35/5/Native American Composers 1942 Nov 3
      III.B/35/13/Southern
      III.B/36/8/Yale Library
      X.D/67/17/Library Correspondence gifts after 1955 and Southern
      - Henry Cowell, 1927 Jul 27; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, 1927 Aug 16; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1927 Aug 20, Dec 4, 1928 Feb 28; 3 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Mar 7; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Mar 24, Mar 27, 1928 Apr 10; 3 typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, [1928 Apr 24?], [1928 May 20]; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 May 25, Jul 10; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - 1928 Jul 13, typed letter (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Jul 26; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, [1928] Aug 12; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Aug 13; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Aug 13; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Aug 20; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell with [notes below], 1928 Sep 13; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 [Sep 20], Oct 3; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, 1928 Oct 11; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Oct 15; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell (verso of programs), [1928 Nov]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Nov 24; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1928 Nov 24; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, [1928 Nov 24?]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, 1928 Dec 3; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1929 Jan 28; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, [1929 Feb 23?]; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Emling, Ralph, 1929 Feb 23; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, [1929 Mar 29]; program with note (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, [1929 Mar 29?]; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1929 Apr 14; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1929 May 20; autograph card signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, [1929?] Jun 1; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, 1929 Aug 29; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1929 Aug 3, Sep 5, 1929 Oct 15, Oct 30; 4 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell with enc of program and book announcement, [1929] Nov 27; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell, 1930 Feb 14, [1930 Mar 18?]; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Charles Ives, [1930 Apr 17?]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - list Charles Ives, [1928-1930?]; **autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Henry Cowell to Charles Ives, 1930 Apr 19, [1930 Apr 22], [1930 Jun 15], [1930 Jul 2], [?1920 Jul 27], 1930 Aug 28; 6 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell to Harmony Twichell Ives, 1930 Sep [?]; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1930 Sep 8; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1930 Sep 22; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1930 Sep 24, Oct 24, 1930 Oct 29, Nov 24, 1930 Nov 26; typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - enc Carol [?] to Henry Cowell, 1930 Nov 26; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1930 Dec 9, 1930 Dec [?); 2 autograph letters signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1931 Jan to Jul; 9 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Charles Ives, 1931 Jul 19; telegram autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1931 Jul to Sep; 6 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Bulletin Ohio State, 1931 Sep 15 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, 1931 Oct to Dec; 6 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Henry Cowell, [?] 1932; typed letter (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Jan 5, Feb 26; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - New Music, 1932 May [?]; card (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Moss Ives, 1932 May 7; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 May 16, May 31; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Aug 15; autograph letter signed card (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - S.F. News, 1932 Jun 1; **article/clipping (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Aug to Sep; 4 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, 1932 [Aug or Sep]; **autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Oct [?], 1932 Oct 16; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Nov 3; negative stat (Box 28, Folder 3)
        (typed transcription by John Kirkpatrick)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Nov 5, Nov 19; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Riegger, 1932 Oct 31; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Charles Ives, [? 1932 Nov 3]; **autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Nov 26; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - with Charles Ives note, 1932 Nov [?]; 2 typed letters (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - (with notes Charles Ives), 1932 Dec 2; **envelope (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Dec 2, Dec 5; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Cowell, Henry, enc of excerpt from Hardcastle Letter (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Dec 11, Dec 12; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1932 Dec 30; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Jan 5, Jan 10, 1933 Jan 14, Jan 20; 4 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - part of letter? Henry Cowell?, 1933 Mar [?]; typed letter (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Feb 14, Feb 16; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - New Music form, 1933 Mar 18; **typed card (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - N. Slonimsky to Henry Cowell, 1933 Mar 29; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - "American Composers on American Music", 1933 Apr; **announcement (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Apr to Jul; 10 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives answer to 1933 Jul 7, **[?] draft (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Jul to Aug; 4 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Golden West Press to Henry Cowell, 1933 Aug 26; typed letter (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Aug to Oct; 5 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, 1933 Oct 31, [?] 1933 Nov 4; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Nov 6; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives to Slonimsky, [?] 1933 Nov; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Nov 7, Nov 8; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, [?] 1933 Nov 12; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Henry Cowell, 1933 Nov 14, Nov 15, 1933 Dec 6; 3 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - (Charles Ives response autograph letter signed on bottom of 1933 Nov 15) (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, [?] 1934; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - A list for New Music, [?] 1933/1934 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Charles Ives, autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1934 Mar]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1934 Apr 27]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1934 Apr 11; typed card signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1934 Apr 24; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1934 Apr 27]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Stone, Christopher to Henry Cowell, 1934 May 11; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, 1934 Jun 3; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1934 Jun 6; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1934] Jun; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1934 Jul 2; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, 1934 Jul to 1935 Feb; 5 autograph letters signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - song list, autograph enc (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?spring 1935]; 2 autograph letters signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1935 Mar 30; typed postcard signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - S.F. Chronicle, 1935 Mar 31; **article (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1935 May]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1935 Jul]; telegram (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1935 Jul]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1935 Jul 8, [?1935]; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, 1935 Jul 26; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1935 Jul 31; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1935 Aug 24; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Charles Ives, [?1935 Aug]; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Henry Cowell, 1935 Aug 28, Oct 4, (with note Charles Ives) 1935 Nov 5, 1935 Dec 30, 1935 Apr [?]; 6 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1940 Aug 14; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Henry Cowell, 1940 Dec 2; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1940 Dec 20; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Henry Cowell, 1940 Dec 23; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Henry Cowell, 1941 Mar 13; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives for, 1941 Apr 16; **draft (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, 1941 Apr 16; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives, no date; **draft (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Henry Cowell enc copy autograph letter signed Christas Vrionedes [?], 1941 Aug 10; typed letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Cowell, Henry, **draft for 1941 Aug 20 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1941 Aug 20; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Henry Cowell, 1941 Aug 23, Sep 15; 2 typed letters signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Charles Ives for 1941 Sep 18, **draft (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, 1941 Sep 18; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Henry Cowell, 1941 Sep 20; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Harmony Twichell Ives, note, 1941 Sep 26; autograph letter signed (Box 28, Folder 6)